tnstate.edu 2006-06-18

# Privacy Policy

_**Copyright Statement**_

All materials contained in this site are protected by United States copyright law. The right to download and store or output the materials on this site is granted for the user's personal, noncommercial use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display, or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without express written permission of Tennessee State University is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on this site may contact us at [**t**](mailto:sbishop@tnstate.edu?subject=Privacy%20Policy) **[he Office of Public Relations](mailto:sbishop@tnstate.edu?subject=Privacy%20Policy).**

© 2003 Tennessee State University All rights reserved. All trademarks mentioned herein belong to their respective owners.

|  ** _Privacy Policy Statement_**

Tennessee State University is fully committed to providing an informative, useful, and entertaining website for its visitors. The university enjoys interacting with its audience and helping to provide it with pertinent information. Visitors to any Tennessee State University webpage have an opportunity to contact us via E-mail. 

The policy of Tennessee State University's officially controlled and operated WWW sites is to respect and protect the privacy of its students, faculty, staff, and all other users. Tennessee State University does not sell or distribute any information obtained from our visitors to a third party, under any circumstance. 

This policy defines how Tennessee State University collects information from you and how it is used. For each visitor to Tennessee State University's website, the following information is collected:   

>   *   **internet addressing information of visitors to our Web pages (IP Addresses)**
>   * **  the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail**
>   * **  the aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit**
>   * **  user-specific information on what pages visitors access or visit**
>   * **  information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information**
>   * **  personal information we request for information inquiries/requests, etc.**
> 

There are cases where Tennessee State University websites may request/or provide personal information such as userID, password, name, or address. To provide for your privacy in these instances, Tennessee State University provides a secure server which transmits and receives scrambled data, which is decoded on the server side. This technology protects your information from being viewed by an outside user. 

The collected information is used for internal University purposes and may be used to improve the content of Tennessee State University's overall website. It will not be shared with other organizations to help them contact visitors. However, Tennessee State University reserves the right to use the information to contact visitors for marketing purposes. 

A small number of Tennessee State University pages contain links which may take you outside of our website. Users should be aware that when you are on, for example, the Tennessee State University Athletics website, and you "click" on a banner advertisement, you will be directed to another website which is beyond Tennessee State University's control. These other sites may send and receive cookies, collect data, or solicit personal information and may use this information in ways Tennessee State University does not in accordance with its privacy policy statement. Always be aware of whose site you are visiting. 

As a WWW user, keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online (i.e. via message boards or chat) information can be collected and used by people you don't even know. 

While Tennessee State University strives to protect its users' personal information and privacy, it cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Tennessee State University's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. 

Tennessee State University reserves the right at its discretion to make changes to this policy at any time. Feel free to check this page periodically for amendments/updates. 

If you do not want to be contacted by us in the future, please let us know. 

| **Our postal address is:  **

    Tennessee State University  
3500 John A. Merritt Blvd.
    Nashville, TN 37209  
(615) 963-5000 or (615) 963-5312
| |   
---|---|---
